### Resume of Yanuo Deng (James)

1565 Cress Way, Olivehurst, CA, 95961 \* (408) 444-5520 \* deng.va.nuo@gmail.com

### CAREER OBJECTIVE

Focused professional with 15+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of embedded system(linux/RTOS), and digital & analogy circuit design. Aming to leverage my skills to be a successfully Integrated Circuit Engineer, Software Engineer, or Network Security Engineer.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## C-MATRIXTECH CO.LTD., Zhuhai, China, 3 person R&D/6

Integrated Circuit Designer, Dec 2017 - Feb 2019

- \* Verilog coding, FPGA simulation and debug for self-powered SOC chip.
- \* MCU debug; Port C-language from Assembly for the MCU; Analog circuit design.
- \* Achieved self-powered MCU SOC used on iPhone data cables; Mass production 10 per month.

### VIOMI CO.LTD., Foshan, China, 3 person R&D/200

Software (Firmware) Engineer, May 2017 - Oct 2017

- \* Linux driver for the wifi chip; Speech Recognition App for Linux.
- \* Achieved smart wireless Speech Recognition module; Mass production 3k per month.

## BLUEWAY CO.LTD., Huizhou, China, 5 person R&D/2500

Software (Firmware) Engineer, May 2016 - Apr 2017

\* FreeRTOS system migration for the embedded board, target for electric mowers.

## ADON CO.LTD., Foshan, China, 3 person R&D/350

Software (Firmware) Engineer, Oct 2013 - Dec 2015

\* Linux driver & app for the Homepod (wifi speaker/charger for iPhone); Mass production, 3k per month.

## SKYIT SOFTWARE CO.LTD., Shunde, China, 5 person R&D/500

Software Engineer, Dec 2011 - Jul 2013

\* Windows Client App by C#; Data API by C for the first order a meal App in China

# VBRIDGE MICROSYSTEM INC, San Jose, CA, 5 person R&D/12

Digital Integrated Circuit Engineer, Apr 2005 - May 2008

- \* AES, DES, 3DES, MD5, SHA1, CRC: IP cores for the security engineer.
- \* 5 bit MCU for the dual-MIPS SOC chip
- \* All IP cores include specification, testbench, RTL; All IP cores verified by the SOC Chip

### **EDUCATION**

XI'AN university of technology, Xi'an city, Shannxi, China

Master of Science (M.S.) Microelectronics & Solidstate Electronics (Apr 2005)

### ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- \* C, Verilog, Vim, Bash, Perl, Go-language, Gnumake, git
- \* Linux / FreeRTOS driver

#### Certifications

Electronics Engineer Certification, Foshan, China, Aug 2008

#### Personal Characteristics

I work well within teams and I am assertive and creative in finding the best solutions for the team. I am known to be stable and firm when coding. I am committed to achieving goals set for me. I speak and write Cantonese/Mandarin.

#### Referrals

Dan Teuthorn, Teledyne microwave solutions, VP engineering, 408-421-7303, Den.Teuthorn@teledyne.com Tang Shanqiang, Cadence, Principal Application Engineer, +65-90546301, ansent@cadence.com Stephen Fung, Atheros/Qualcomm, semicondutor Engineer, 408-338-5175, stephen@thepoint.church

USA Employment Authorization Document (EAD) valided from 2021 to 2023. No work sponsor is needed.